Guide to the Records of the NYU TV and Media Services Video Recordings RG.38.16.1
New York University Archives
NYU TV and Media Services Video Recordings
1993-2017
New York University Archives
New York University
NYU-TV
RG.38.16.1
33.75 Linear Feet
656 Megabytes on 1 recording
This collection contains videotapes from the NYU TV and Media Services department, part of the Division of Libraries. The videotapes come from NYU-TV and the Television Center (TVCenter), two of the three departments within NYU TV and Media Services, and include both NYU-produced and commercially produced television shows, educational programming, and recordings of NYU events from 1993 to 2017.
Arrangement
The items in this collection are organized into one series of general videotapes from NYU TV and another series of Commencement and Founder's Day.
Custodial History
The videotapes within this collection came to the University Archives in multiple accessions from the Division of Libraries. In April 2018 an accretion of one born-digital video recording was transferred to the Archives; the accession number associated with this transfer is 2018.012.
Scope and Contents
The material within this collection comes from the NYU-TV and TVCenter departments. The NYU-TV material includes both professionally and NYU-produced television shows covering a range of television genres, including sketch comedy, soap operas, science fiction, cooking and travel, as well as educational and informational documentaries. The TVCenter material predominantly covers various Founder's Day and Commencement ceremonies.
Separated Materials
There is no information about materials that are associated by provenance to the described materials that have been physically separated or removed.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the commercially produced recordings is restricted. NYU-produced recordings are open without restrictions.
Historical Note
NYU TV and Media Services, part of the Division of Libraries, was founded in the early 1990s to provide cable and video production services to the university. Since its inception, it has grown to include three separate departments: NYU-TV, the Television Center, and Campus Cable. NYU-TV comprises the university's closed-circuit channels used for information, education, and entertainment purposes and is broadcast in campus buildings and residence halls. The TV Center is home to NYU-TV and serves as the NYU community's resource for video production. Campus Cable is the multi-channel television system serving the NYU residence halls and is made up of traditional cable as well as NYU-TV channels.
Source:
NYU-TV and Media Services. "About Us." NYU TV and Media Services. http://www.nyu.edu/tv.media/about.us/.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Access to some audiovisual materials in this collection is available through digitized access copies. Researchers may view an item's original container, but the media themselves are not available for playback because of preservation concerns. Materials that have already been digitized are noted in the collection's finding aid and can be requested in our reading room.
Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact university-archives@nyu.edu with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Advance notice is required for the use of computer records. Original physical digital media is restricted. An access terminal for born-digital materials in the collection is available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Researchers may view an item's original container and/or carrier, but the physical carriers themselves are not available for use because of preservation concerns.
New York University. Library Division.; Video recordings.; Videocassettes.; New York University
- Series I: Video Recordings, 1993-2005; 219087
  General note
  Barcode:
  - Gamma 51, undated; cuid673; 219182; 8 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 1, Reel Project 1)
    Barcode: 31142042272743
  - Air Raid, undated; cuid674; 219181; 17 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 1, Reel Project 2)
  - Industry Attractions, undated; cuid675; 219180; 3 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 1, Reel Project 3)
  - Offline, undated; cuid676; 219179; 29 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 1, Reel Project 4)
    Barcode: 31142042272750
  - UNET, 1992-1995; cuid677; 219178; 18 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 2, Reel Project 5)
  - Fast Forward: Contemporary Science Fiction: Episodes 53-71, 75-79, 91, 1994-1997; cuid678; 219177; 16 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 3, Reel Project 7)
    Barcode: 31142042272768
  - Bay State, undated; cuid679; 219176; 4 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 3, Reel Project 8)
  - Children's Television Workshop: Ghostwriter, 1992; cuid680; 219175; 2 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 2, Reel Project 6)
  - Promos, undated; cuid681; 219174; 19 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 3, Reel Project 9)
  - Burly Bear Network: Tapes 1-19B, 1997-1998; cuid682; 219173; 20 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 4, Reel Project 10)
    Barcode: 31142042272776
  - Avery Fischer Center Promo, 1991; cuid683; 219172; 2 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 5, Reel Project 11)
    Barcode: 31142042272784
  - NYU Founders Day, April 20, 1997; cuid684; 219171; 2 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 5, Reel Project 12)
  - Legislative Advocacy: How to Effectively Communicate with Elected Officials, undated; cuid685; 219170; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 5, Reel Project 13)
  - European Teleconference, April 24, 1997; cuid686; 219169; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 5, Reel Project 14)
  - King Juan Carlos of Spain, April 9, 1997; cuid687; 219168; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 5, Reel Project 15)
  - Deaf President Now: The Pulse of the People, undated; cuid688; 219167; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 5, Reel Project 16)
  - Dialog On-Line Seach, December 5, 1995; cuid689; 219166; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 5, Reel Project 17)
  - Emerging Writers, December 8, 1994; cuid690; 219165; 3 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 5, Reel Project 18)
  - Andrea Sherman Lecture Masters, undated; cuid691; 219163; 3 videocassettes (Box 5, Reel Project 20)
  - C-Team Traning Session, 20 Feb 1996; cuid692; 219162; 3 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 5, Reel Project 21)
  - C-Team B-Roll Betamax, 26 Mar 1996; cuid693; 219161; 3 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 5, Reel Project 22)
  - Distance Learning VHS, March 9, 1996; cuid694; 219160; 2 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 5, Reel Project 23)
  - Mary Anne and B. Roll, undated; cuid695; 219159; 2 videocassettes (hi8) (Box 5, Reel Project 24)
  - Assistive Technology, May 3, 1996; cuid696; 219158; 3 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 5, Reel Project 25)
  - Interview with President Oliva, August 8, 1995; cuid697; 219157; 4 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 6, Reel Project 26)
    Barcode: 31142042272792
  - DeWitt Clinton Award Dinner for Morris Sullivan, December 18, 1992; cuid698; 219156; 5 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 6, Reel Project 27)
  - Dukakis Cam 2, August 11, 1998; cuid699; 219155; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 6, Reel Project 28)
  - Reel to Real: Jeff Lipsky, undated; cuid700; 219154; 2 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 6, Reel Project 29)
  - Deconstruction Roundtable: Jacques Derrida, undated; cuid701; 219153; 2 videocassettes (Box 6, Reel Project 30)
  - President's Service Awards, 1996; cuid702; 219152; 2 videocassettes (Box 6, Reel Project 31)
  - Commerce and the Net, December 1, 1995; cuid703; 219151; 2 videocassettes (Box 6, Reel Project 32)
  - Interview with Vandana Shiva, March 23, 1992; cuid704; 219150; 1 videocassettes (Box 6, Reel Project 33)
  - AmeriCorps Convocation, October 14, 1994; cuid705; 219149; 1 videocassettes (Box 6, Reel Project 34)
  - Mentoring USA, September 1996; cuid706; 219148; 2 videocassettes (betacamsp) (Box 7, Reel Project 35)
    Barcode: 31142042272800
  - Dialog Studio Shoot in Bobst Library, December 6, 1995; cuid707; 219147; 1 videocassettes (Box 7, Reel Project 36)
  - Patterns of Adjustment, undated; cuid708; 219146; 40 videocassettes (Box 7, Reel Project 37)
  - SHTEIG-95, undated; cuid709; 219145; 4 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 7, Reel Project 38)
  - NYU Earth Summit, March 27, 1992; cuid710; 219144; 4 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 7, Reel Project 39)
  - Emerging Writers, undated; cuid711; 219143; 3 videocassettes (Box 7, Reel Project 18)
  - Burly Bear Network, undated; cuid712; 219142; 9 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 8, Reel Project 10)
    Barcode: 31142042272818
  - Rights & Wrongs, undated; cuid713; 219141; 25 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 8, Reel Project 40)
  - NASA CORE, undated; cuid714; 219140; 5 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 9, Reel Project 41)
    Barcode: 31142042272826
  - CNBC "Smart Living", October 1993; cuid715; 219139; 1 videocassettes (Box 9, Reel Project 42)
  - Burly Bear Network, 1998; cuid716; 219138; 0 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 9, Reel Project 10)
  - Rights & Wrongs, 1996; cuid717; 219137; 14 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 10, Reel Project 40)
    Barcode: 31142042272834
  - Fast Forward: Contemporary Science Fiction, undated; cuid718; 219136; 10 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 10, Reel Project 7)
  - Meet the Professor, undated; cuid719; 219135; 3 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 10, Reel Project 43)
  - Exploring the Internet: Part 2, undated; cuid720; 219134; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 10, Reel Project 44)
  - Video Art and Virtual Reality, undated; cuid721; 219133; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 10, Reel Project 45)
  - Goals 2000, undated; cuid722; 219132; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 10, Reel Project 46)
  - Building Partnerships, undated; cuid723; 219131; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 10, Reel Project 47)
  - Colour Connections, undated; cuid724; 219130; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 10, Reel Project 48)
  - Students With Disabilities, undated; cuid725; 219129; 2 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 10, Reel Project 49)
  - Work Spirit, undated; cuid726; 219128; 2 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 10, Reel Project 50)
  - Office of the Presidency, undated; cuid727; 219127; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 10, Reel Project 51)
  - Peace Corps Teleconference, undated; cuid728; 219126; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 10, Reel Project 52)
  - New York Windows, undated; cuid729; 219125; 10 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 10, Reel Project 53)
  - Off the Cuff, undated; cuid730; 219124; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 11, Reel Project 54)
    Barcode: 31142042272842
  - Career Services, 1992; cuid731; 219123; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 11, Reel Project 55)
  - Eggplant, undated; cuid732; 219122; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 11, Reel Project 56)
  - NYU Student Voice on Campus, undated; cuid733; 219121; 29 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 11, Reel Project 57)
  - UNET, 1994-1996; cuid734; 219120 (Box 11, Reel Project 5)
  - Career Connection, undated; cuid735; 219119; 3 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 11, Reel Project 58)
  - CCTV, undated; cuid736; 219118; 5 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 11, Reel Project 59)
  - NYU Law Forum, 21 Sep 1998; cuid737; 219117; 13 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 12, Reel Project 60)
    Barcode: 31142042272859
  - Hartford Institute for Geriatric Nursing Development Conference, June 1999; cuid738; 219116; 6 videocassettes (Box 47)
  - New York University Works In Progress, 1999; cuid739; 219115; 4 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 47)
  - The 3rd Annual Schmio Awards, April 1999; cuid740; 219114; 4 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 47)
  - Best Nursing Practices in Care for Older Adults: Incorporating Geriatric Content into Undergraduate Education and Staff Development, June 1999; cuid741; 219113; 1 videocassettes (Box 47)
  - Charlie's Family Portrait WABC, February 1999; cuid742; 219112; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 47)
  - Albany Day, 1997-1998; cuid743; 219111; 12 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 48)
  - Publication of Stone and Steel, March 1998; cuid744; 219110; 3 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 48)
  - Dean Daly Stern Betamax, 25 March 1998; cuid745; 219643 (Box 48)
  - Ehrenkranz School of Social Work Advocacy Orientation Betamax, 23 July 1998; cuid746; 219644; 2 videocassettes (Box 48)
  - Yale Strom-Hot P'Stromi, November 1998; cuid747; 219109; 2 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 48)
  - Alix Kates Shulman, October 1997; cuid748; 219108; 3 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 48)
  - Highlight Loop, 1998; cuid749; 219107; 2 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 48)
  - Digital Libraries Bobst, 1998; cuid750; 219106; 9 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 49)
  - HeadStart Teleconference, 1997; cuid751; 219105; 4 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 49)
  - Interviews, Undated; cuid752; 219104; 1 videocassettes (Box 49)
  - Peter Campus - Art Gallery Meet the Professor, undated; cuid753; 219103; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 49)
  - Cinema TV Master Original, October 1996; cuid754; 219102; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 49)
  - Beyond Race by Paul Sniderman, 24 Feb 1997; cuid755; 219101; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 49)
  - The Dental School Project, Undated; cuid756; 219100; 3 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 50)
  - New York University Winter Stock Footage, undated; cuid757; 219099; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 50)
  - Gender Bender, Nov 1996; cuid758; 219098; 4 videocassettes (Box 50, Cassette cuid758, E-records nyuarchives_rg38.16.1, E-records cuid758)
  - Black Genius Series - Angela Davis and Spike Lee, 1996-1997; cuid759; 219097; 2 videocassettes (Box 50)
  - The Neil Brownbag Speech, Undated; cuid760; 219096; 2 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 50)
  - Internet Future, June 1997; cuid761; 219095; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 50)
  - Richard Maass Lecture, undated; cuid762; 219094; 2 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 50)
  - European Teleconference: European Union and American Union, 24 April 1997; cuid763; 219645; 6 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 50)
  - Things To Do In Denver When You're Dead, November 1995; cuid764; 219093; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 50)
  - Club Fair Loop, undated; cuid765; 219092; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 50)
  - All University Sing, 1994-1998; cuid766; 219646; 6 videocassettes (Box 51)
  - 55th Institute on Federal Taxation: Legislative Highlights, 29 Sep 1996; cuid767; 219647; 2 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 51)
  - New York University Gospel Choir, 12 Dec 1996; cuid768; 219648; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 51)
  - Black Genius Betamax, cuid769; 219649; 4 videocassettes (Box 51)
  - Soaring to Excellence: You and the Internet, undated; cuid770; 219650; 1 videocassettes (Box 51)
  - Hillary Rodham Clinton NYU Americorp VHS, 9 April 1997; cuid771; 219651; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 51)
  - King Juan Carlos of Spain NYU, 9 April 1997; cuid772; 219652; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 51)
  - Protecting Your Campus from Crime: Challenges and Solutions, 17 Nov 1997; cuid773; 219653; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 51)
  - Asian American Conference, 1997; cuid774; 219654; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 51)
  - Bobst Library: The Heart of the University Edit Master, 1994; cuid775; 219091; 1 videocassettes (betacamsp) (Box 52, Reel Project 6)
  - Soaring to Excellence, 3 March 1997; cuid776; 219655; 4 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 52)
  - Culture and Poverty in the Clinton Era, 10 Feb 1998; cuid777; 219656; 4 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 52)
  - Time Warner Cable, undated; cuid778; 219657; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 52)
  - Stern Business School Conference Guest Speaker, 23 April 1997; cuid779; 219658; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 52)
  - Works in Progress, 10 March 1998; cuid780; 219659; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 52)
  - Defending Ourselves Against the Seductions of Eloquence Neil Postman, 16 Feb 1994; cuid781; 219660; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 52)
    Existence and Location of Copies
    Access copy available on DVD: ACCESS 6:3.
  - What it Means for New York City, 18 June 1996; cuid782; 219661; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 52)
  - Award Dinner Articles, undated; cuid783; 219662; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 52)
  - OJ Verdict NYU Students Reacts, 3 Oct 1995; cuid784; 219663; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 52)
  - Boxing After Dark, undated; cuid785; 219664; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 52)
  - New York University Life in the Greenwich Village, undated; cuid786; 219665; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 52)
  - Summer in Paris, 1996; cuid787; 219666; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 52)
  - Fair Use Guidellines Satellite Downlink, 20 Feb 1997; cuid788; 219667; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 52)
  - Dancing With Change, 05 Dec 1997; cuid789; 219668; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 52)
  - The City and the University, undated; cuid790; 219750; 3 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 53)
  - Spike Lee Lecture at Tishman Auditorium, 18 Oct 1996; cuid791; 219753; 1 videocassettes (Box 53)
  - The Helping Hand, undated; cuid792; 219756; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 53)
  - Nursing Public Service Announcement, 28 April 1995; cuid793; 219757; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 53)
  - Science at New York University, undated; cuid794; 219758; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 53)
  - Yale Strom - Hot P'Stromi, 11 Nov 1998; cuid795; 219761; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 53)
  - Wagner Labor Archives, 20 Oct 1995; cuid796; 219764; 2 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 53)
  - Evening Magazine, 28 Sept 1998; cuid797; 219766; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 53)
  - Tamiment Oral History Gil Greene, 23 Jan 1991; cuid798; 219768; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 53)
  - Post Operative Recovery, 14 June 1994; cuid799; 219771; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 53)
  - Video Production Center, 28 Mar 1994; cuid800; 219774; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 53)
  - The Telecommunications Act of 1996: What it Means for NYC, 18 June 1996; cuid801; 219779; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 53)
  - Leslie Harris Interview, undated; cuid802; 219780; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 53)
  - Dr. Peskin Heart Warren Weaver Hall, undated; cuid803; 219782; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 53)
  - Andrea Sherman Lecture, 24 June 1997; cuid804; 219785; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 53)
  - Campus Media Shots, undated; cuid805; 219788; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 53)
  - Media Services Compilation Tape, undated; cuid806; 219790; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 53)
  - Ken Roth at New York University, 18 Sept 1995; cuid807; 219795; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 54)
  - Fort Lauderdale Film Festival Trailer, undated; cuid808; 219797; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 54)
  - Kristen Linklater at New York University, 9 Oct 1995; cuid809; 219801; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 54)
  - "The Time is Out of Joint" Jacques Derrida Speech, 7 Oct 1993; cuid810; 219802; 2 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 54)
  - Americorp Convocation, 14 Oct 1994; cuid811; 219806; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 54)
  - Mary Gordon at New York University, 02 Oct 1995; cuid812; 219808; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 54)
  - Seward Park Conflict Resolution Class Simulation, undated; cuid813; 219811; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 54)
  - Video Production Center, March 1993; cuid814; 219813; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 54)
  - Dialog Final Master, undated; cuid815; 219816; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 54)
  - King Juan Carlos in Bobst, 9 April 1997; cuid816; 219819; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 54)
  - Women's Health, undated; cuid817; 219822; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 54)
  - Law School Blank, undated; cuid818; 219823; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 54)
  - Dunbar Michael Dorf Knitting Factory, 16 Nov 1998; cuid819; 219824; 1 videocassettes (Box 54)
  - Questioning Media with Neil Postman, 11 July 1996; cuid820; 219827; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 55)
    Multiple Tapes
    This Item is split onto two tapes.
    Access copy available on 2 DVDs: ACCESS 6:1 & 6:2.
  - Benefits Seminar, undated; cuid821; 219830; 2 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 55)
  - Social Work Orientation Web Site, 25 Aug 1998; cuid822; 219831; 2 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 55)
  - Financial Aid Project, undated; cuid823; 219833; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 55)
  - Dr. Ruth Lecture, 1 Nov 1995; cuid824; 219834; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 55)
  - Dukakis Press Conference, undated; cuid825; 219839; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 55)
  - Industry Attractions, undated; cuid826; 219840; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 55)
  - Advocacy in Social Work, July 1998; cuid827; 219843; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 55)
  - Race, Gender, and the Role of Scholars in Contemporary American Society, undated; cuid828; 219881; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 55)
  - Dr. Kallembach Chem Lab Laser Lab, March 1993; cuid829; 219918; 3 videocassettes (betacam) (Box 56)
  - Old Photos of Bobst, August 1994; cuid830; 219090; 1 videocassettes (betacamsp) (Box 56, Reel Project 10)
  - Hester Interview Part 2, Septemebr 1994; cuid831; 219089; 1 videocassettes (betacamsp) (Box 56, Reel Project 10)
  - Bobst Exteriors still photos, undated; cuid832; 219088; 1 videocassettes (betacam) (Box 56, Reel Project 10)
  - Leslie Harris Interview, 22 April 1997; cuid833; 219923; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 56)
  - On-going Recovery Program, Undated; cuid834; 219926; 4 videocassettes (betacam) (Box 56)
  - Heart Shaped Video Box, 3 Feb 1994; cuid835; 219932; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 56)
  - Triangle Waistshirt Footage, undated; cuid836; 219934; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 56)
  - The Return of the Hollywood Studio System, 29 Oct 1996; cuid837; 219936; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 56)
  - Americorps Conference on Conflict Resolution Training for Grad Students, undated; cuid838; 219937; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 56)
  - End of Training Conference Clinton Cutaways, undated; cuid839; 219943; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 56)
  - New York University Benefits Office Developing a Savings Strategy, undated; cuid840; 219949; 1 videocassettes (Box 56)
  - New York University School of Law, undated; cuid841; 219951; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 56)
  - Stone and Steel Fales Library, 3 March 1998; cuid842; 219952; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 56)
  - Regional Assitance Center Video Conference, 31 Oct 1996; cuid843; 219954; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 56)
  - Health Services Grand Opening, 9 March 1998; cuid844; 219956; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 56)
  - Woman Kind, 30 March 1996; cuid845; 219961; 1 videocassettes (Box 56)
  - Long Distance Learning Seminar, undated; cuid846; 219963; 1 videocassettes (Box 56)
  - Integrating Media and Instruction, 1994; cuid847; 219964; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 56)
  - Andrea Sherman Lecture, undated; cuid848; 220085; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 57, Reel 11)
  - New York University Benefits Office Developing an Investment Strategy, undated; cuid849; 220086; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 57, Reel 11)
  - Steven J. Gould Accidental Human Presence in the Age Bacteria, 16 Oct 1996; cuid850; 220087 (Box 57, Cassette cuid850, E-records nyuarchives_rg38.16.1, E-records cuid850)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Format: VHS, Duration: 93 min.
  - Last Takes of Catherine AFC Shots, undated; cuid851; 220088; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 57, Reel 11)
  - "NYU Animal Training" Dub Master, 4 Oct 1994; cuid852; 220089; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 57, Reel 11)
  - AFC and Library Pick ups and Mike Part 1, undated; cuid853; 220090; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 57, Reel 11)
  - Ivo Ezeta New York University -TV Anim, June 1995; cuid854; 220091; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 57, Reel 11)
  - Yale Strom Hot P'Stromi, 4 Nov 1998; cuid855; 220092; 2 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 57, Reel 11)
  - Mike Marcinelli Pt. 2 Dana at Nursing Workstation, undated; cuid856; 220093; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 57, Reel 11)
  - Interview with Kassandra Goins; Tuff Gong; Jamaica Segment; Anastasra Bard/Claudine Athens, 17 July 1997; cuid857; 220094; 1 videocassettes (betamax) (Box 57, Reel 11)
  - NYU Science Video Dub of 1st Part, undated; cuid858; 220095; 3 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 57, Reel 11)